const level10Questions = [
  {
        question: "Điền Phương",
        answers: ["马 (mǎ)", "田芳 (Tián Fāng)"],
        correct: "田芳 (Tián Fāng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ái Đức Hoa, Edward",
        answers: ["爱德华 (Àidéhuá)", "罗兰 (Luólán)"],
        correct: "爱德华 (Àidéhuá)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ngôn ngữ",
        answers: ["语言 (yǔyán)", "大学 (dàxué)"],
        correct: "语言 (yǔyán)",
    },
    {
        question: "Thế nào, ra sao, như thế nào",
        answers: ["怎么样 (zěnmeyàng)", "觉得 (juéde)"],
        correct: "怎么样 (zěnmeyàng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Cảm thấy",
        answers: ["觉得 (juéde)", "语法 (yǔfǎ)"],
        correct: "觉得 (juéde)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nghe",
        answers: ["听 (tīng)", "和 (hé)"],
        correct: "听 (tīng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nói",
        answers: ["说 (shuō)", "比较 (bǐjiào)"],
        correct: "说 (shuō)",
    },
    {
        question: "Tương đối",
        answers: ["比较 (bǐjiào)", "容易 (róngyì)"],
        correct: "比较 (bǐjiào)",
    },
    {
        question: "Dễ",
        answers: ["容易 (róngyì)", "读 (dú)"],
        correct: "容易 (róngyì)",
    },
    {
        question: "Đọc",
        answers: ["读 (dú)", "写 (xiě)"],
        correct: "读 (dú)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nhưng",
        answers: ["但是 (dànshì)", "给 (gěi)"],
        correct: "但是 (dànshì)",
    },
    {
        question: "Mới",
        answers: ["新 (xīn)", "北京语言大学 (Běijīng Yǔyán Dàxué)"],
        correct: "新 (xīn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Bạn cùng phòng",
        answers: ["同学 (tóngxué)", "同屋 (tóngwū)"],
        correct: "同屋 (tóngwū)",
    },
    {
        question: "Lâm",
        answers: ["班 (bān)", "林 (Lín)"],
        correct: "林 (Lín)",
    },
    {
        question: "Vali, thùng, hộp",
        answers: ["没有 (méiyǒu)", "箱子 (xiāngzi)"],
        correct: "箱子 (xiāngzi)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ở đây",
        answers: ["有 (yǒu)", "这儿 (zhèr)"],
        correct: "这儿 (zhèr)",
    },
];

export default level10Questions;
